

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211





PALLAM TRIPATHI PALLAVI TRIPATHI (1) Featured Support Analyst seeking roles in Application Support, System Support, Security Management, Business Analysis, Performance Tuning, Resource Planning, Data Validation, SLA Management, Requirement Gathering, Data Management, Report Generation, HTML, CSS, PHP Current Designation: Support Analyst Total Experience: 1 Year(s) 3 Month(s) Current Company: Data Resolve Technologies Notice Period: 15 Days or less Current Location: Chennai Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers] Pref. Location: Chennai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance Role: Tech Support Enanr Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Married Key Skills: support analyst, tech support engineer, application support, system support, security management,

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21 Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

report generation, advanced excel Verified : Number | Email - id

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Result-oriented Professional with over 1 years of experience in Application Support, System Support, Security Management, Business Analysis, Performance Tuning, Resource Planning, Data Validation, SLA Management, Requirement Gathering, Data Management, Report Generation, HTML, CSS, PHP

performance tuning, resource planning, data validation, sla management, requirement gathering, data management,

Work Experience

Data Resolve Technologies as Support Analyst

Sep 2018 to Nov 2019

Role and Responsibility.-

Carried out monthly performance tracking for all business avenues and conducted analysis of the product. -Worked on Fresh desk tool and Chat bot process. -Worked on Excel sheet and made records of all the projects. -Solved L1 issues.

.Freshdesk Tool -Assigned Tickets -Created Tickets/ Account -Updated ticket status -Followed up Tech and Maintain sheet of all the tickets. -Created / Modified customers contacts -Created/Maintain sheet of all the tickets -Document Review on portal and Updating Data -Escalation Ticket tracking and Maintenance.

Chat Bot Process - Chat with clients for their issues and solved them.

P & L process (Profit &Loss) - Created/Maintain of P & L Account of the projects. - Created/Maintain Collection and delivery phase's sheet -Created/Maintain Daily Delivery Activity Tracker sheet -Created/Maintain Delivery cost tracker sheet of the projects

Handling customers issues on call

Managed resources performance

Solved issues as per SLA

Expert in intermediate excel

Prepared Cyber intelligence report

Maintain and track of tasks at team member level with due dates assigned to each tasks

Follow-ups on due dates and closures by speaking to respective member Generated performance reports of Each

Delivery and Presales Team member and running analysis on the same

Liase regarding closure of presales and delivery tasks

Maintain calendar with teams for respective follow-up

Ensured that Team KRAs are matching with what they doing and overall if their monthly goals are being met or not

Ensured each Presales member is adhering to Presales Operational Guidelines Ensured each Delivery Member is adhering to Delivery Operational Guidelines

Agent Installation in Windows

Mac Agent Installation in Linux.

Server Update

Policy Creation and Testing

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Data Resolve Technologies as Support Analyst

Sep 2018 to Nov 2019

Carrying out monthly performance tracking for all business avenues and conducting analysis of the product. - Working on FreshDesk tool and chat bot process.

- Working on Excel sheet and make records of all the projects.
- Solving L1 issues

1-Freshdesk

Assigning Ticket Create Tickets/Account

Update ticket status

Chase Tech and Support for closing tickets.

Creating/ Maintaining sheet of all the tickets.
Create / Modify customers contacts

2- Chat Bot Process- chat with clients for their issues

3- PnL process(Profit &Loss)

Creating/Maintaining of PnL Account of the projects.
Creating/Maintaining Collection and delivery phases sheet

Creating/Maintaining Daily Delivery Activity Tracker sheet

Creating/Maintaining Delivery cost tracker sheet of the projects.

- 4- Handling customers issues on call
- 5- Managing resources performance
- 6- Solving issues as per SLA
- 7- Expert in intermediate excel
- 8- Prepared Cyber intelligence Report

Data Resolve Technologies as Support Analyst

Sep 2018 to Till Date

Carrying out monthly performance tracking for all business avenues and conducting analysis of the product.

- Working on FreshDesk tool and chat bot process
- Working on Excel sheet and make records of all the projects.
- Solving L1 issues

1-Freshdesk

Assigning Ticket Create Tickets/ Account

Update ticket status

Chase Tech and Support for closing tickets.

Creating/ Maintaining sheet of all the tickets. Create / Modify customers contacts

2- Chat Bot Process- chat with clients for their issues

3- PnL process(Profit &Loss)
Creating/Maintaining of PnL Account of the projects.
Creating/Maintaining Collection and delivery phases sheet
Creating/Maintaining Daily Delivery Activity Tracker sheet
Creating/Maintaining Delivery cost tracker sheet of the projects.
4- Handling customers issues on call

- 5- Managing resources performance 6- Solving issues as per SLA
- 7- Expert in intermediate excel
- 8- Prepared Cyber intelligence Report

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from united college of engineering and management in 2018

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
Microsoft Office	Advanced	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
C, C++, PHP, HTML,CSS				
Advanced Excel	Advanced	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Pivot Table	Advanced	2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Incident Management	Advanced	2019	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
VLOOKUP	Advanced	2020	1 Year(s) 3 Month(s)	
HLOOKUP	Advanced	2020	1 Year(s) 3 Month(s)	
Online Marketing		2019	1 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	

^ Back to Top

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.